software-testing-tutorials-automation.com 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy

**  
****What Information Do We Collect?**  
We collect Information when you subscribe to get post updates via email and fill up forms.

**What Do We Use Your Information For?**  
Any of the Information we collect from you may be used In one of the following ways.

  * To Improve our website.
  * To send new blog post email notification. Any time you can unsubscribe from these notification emails.

**Do We Use Cookies?**  
We do not use cookies.

**Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally Identifiable Information. This does not Include trusted third parties who assist us In operating our blog, or serving you, so long as those parties agree to keep this Information confidential.

**Third Party Links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may Include or offer third party products or services on our blog. These third party sites have separate and Independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the Integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to Information collected through our blog and not to Information collected offline.

**Your Consent**  
By using our blog, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changing To Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, We will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 16/11/2014.
